Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - N
        - Notorious B.I.G. - Duets: the final chapter (disc two), 2005; SR-24544; Notorious B.I.G. (Box 375)
          Catalog # 83885-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-83885C-2
        - Notwist - Shrink, 1998; SR-24545; Notwist (Box 375)
          Catalog # COM 1010-236-1; A-side Matrix # B812290-01 A1 KL
          Community
        - Novel - The first chapter (better days), 2003; SR-24546; Novel (Box 375)
          Catalog # MCAR-25987-1; A-side Matrix # MCAR 259871-A
          Rawkus
        - Novel - The first chapter (better days), 2003; SR-24547; Novel (Box 375)
        - Novo Combo - The animation generation, 1982; SR-24548; Novo Combo (Box 375)
          Catalog # 2391 550; A-side Matrix # 160 2391550 1 380
        - N.P.C. - Georgia bounce, 1994; SR-24549; N.P.C.; L.A. Sno Of Duice (Box 375)
          Catalog # 01624-15525-1; A-side Matrix # 01624-15525-1-A
          Woburn, Massachusetts
        - N.R.G. U.K - Band of gold, 1990; SR-24550; N.R.G. U.K; Ellie (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24551
          Catalog # SYRT 16; A-side Matrix # SYRT 16 A-1U-1-1
          Swanyard Records Ltd
        - N.R.G. U.K - Band of gold, 1990; SR-24551; N.R.G. U.K; Ellie (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24550
        - *NSYNC - Bye bye bye (the remixes), 2000; SR-24552; *NSYNC (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24553. 2 copies. Annotated. Promo
          Catalog # JDAB-42681-1; A-side Matrix # 01241-42681-1-A
          Jive
        - *NSYNC - Bye bye bye (the remixes), 2000; SR-24553; *NSYNC (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24552. 2 copies.Promo
        - N.T. Gang - Wam bam, 1988; SR-24554; N.T. Gang (Box 375)
          Catalog # COOLX 163; A-side Matrix # COOLX 163 A3
        - Nu Colours - Fallin down, 1993; SR-24555; Nu Colours (Box 375)
          Catalog # 867-327-1DJ; A-side Matrix # 867-327-1-A
        - Nu Flavor - Sweet sexy thing, 1997; SR-24556; Nu Flavor; Roger; Troutman, Roger (Box 375)
          Catalog # 0-43865; A-side Matrix # 0-43865-A-SR1
        - Nu-Flex - All you're gonna do (is dance), 1988; SR-24557; Nu-Flex (Box 375)
          Catalog # LIG-505; A-side Matrix # LIG-505-A 1-1
          Ligosa Records
        - Nu Romance Crew - Tonight, 1987; SR-24558; Nu Romance Crew (Box 375)
          Catalog # V-19240; A-side Matrix # V1-19240-Z1
        - Nu Shooz - I can't wait, 1986; SR-24559; Nu Shooz (Box 375)
          Catalog # DMD 920; A-side Matrix # ST DM 49073-1
        - Nu Shooz - Should I say yes?, 1988; SR-24560; Nu Shooz (Box 375)
          Catalog # DMD 1155; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-54283-54286-1
        - Nu Shooz - Point of no return, 1986; SR-24561; Nu Shooz (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24562. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # DMD 951; A-side Matrix # STDM 49747-1
        - Nu Shooz - Point of no return, 1986; SR-24562; Nu Shooz (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24561. 2 copies.Promo
        - Nu Soul Habits - Cross my heart, 1995; SR-24563; Nu Soul Habits (Box 375)
          Catalog # 374631290-1; A-side Matrix # 37463-1290-1-A-SP1
        - Nu Sounds - Condition red, 1989; SR-24564; Nu Sounds (Box 375)
          Catalog # UNI-8016; A-side Matrix # UNI-8864-HF1
          UNI Records
        - Nu-Sounds - Body slam, 1989; SR-24565; Nu-Sounds; Afrika Bambaataa; Silas, Louil, Jr. (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24566. 2 copies.
          Catalog # UNI-8022; A-side Matrix # UNI9367 FDS-1
        - Nu-Sounds - Body slam, 1989; SR-24566; Nu-Sounds; Afrika Bambaataa; Silas, Louil, Jr. (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24565. 2 copies.
        - Nu-Sounds - Mackin', 1989; SR-24567; Nu-Sounds (Box 375)
          Catalog # UNI-12; A-side Matrix # UNI-9360 HF1
        - Nuance - Take a chance, 1984; SR-24568; Nuance; Love, Vikki (Box 375)
          Catalog # PRO 403; A-side Matrix # BWAY-403-PRO-403-A
        - Nuance - Take a chance, 1984; SR-24569; Nuance; Love, Vikki (Box 375)
        - Nubian Crackers - As them talk, 1993; SR-24570; Nubian Crackers; Don-T (Box 375)
          Catalog # 0-10136; A-side Matrix # STDM-66004-66005-66006-1
          Big Beat
        - Nubian Crackers - As them talk, 1993; SR-24571; Nubian Crackers; Don-T (Box 375)
        - Nucci Rey O - Mami u know u got it, 2001; SR-24572; Nucci Rey O (Box 375)
          Catalog # MCAR-25469-1; A-side Matrix # MCAR-25469-1A
        - Nugent, Ted - Survival of the fittest - live, 1971; SR-24573; Nugent, Ted; Amboy Dukes (Box 375)
          Catalog # 24-4035; A-side Matrix # 24-4035-POLP-80109-1-1-1
        - Numan, Gary - Complex, 1979; SR-24574; Numan, Gary (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24575. 2 copies.
          Catalog # BEG 29(T); A-side Matrix # BEG 29T A-1
          Beggars Banquet
        - Numan, Gary - Complex, 1979; SR-24575; Numan, Gary (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24574. 2 copies.
        - Numan, Gary - Cars | Tom Sawyer, 2003; SR-24576; Numan, Gary; Rush (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24577. 2 copies.
          Catalog # AO-9525; A-side Matrix # AO 9525 A
          Alpha Omega Recordings
        - Numan, Gary - Cars | Tom Sawyer, 2003; SR-24577; Numan, Gary; Rush (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24576. 2 copies.
        - Numan, Gary - Your fascination, 1985; SR-24578; Numan, Gary (Box 375)
          Catalog # NUM 9; A-side Matrix # NUM-9-A-1
          Numa
        - Numan, Gary - Music for chameleons, 1982; SR-24579; Numan, Gary (Box 375)
          Catalog # BEG 70T; A-side Matrix # BEG-70-TA
        - Numan, Gary - Exhibition (disc one), 1987; SR-24580; Numan, Gary (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24581. Double album.
          Catalog # BEGA 88; A-side Matrix # BEGA-88-A-1
        - Numan, Gary - Exhibition (disc two), 1987; SR-24581; Numan, Gary (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24580. Double album.
          Catalog # BEGA 88; A-side Matrix # BEGA-88-C-1
        - Numan, Gary - Cars, 1987; SR-24582; Numan, Gary (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24583. Different discs.
          Catalog # BEG 199T; A-side Matrix # BEG-199 (T) A-1
        - Numan, Gary - Cars, 1987; SR-24583; Numan, Gary (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24582. Different discs.
          Catalog # BEG 199TR; A-side Matrix # BEG-199 TR-A1
        - Numan, Gary - Random mixes of Gary Numan 2.1, 1997; SR-24584; Numan, Gary (Box 375)
          Catalog # RANDOM 2.1; A-side Matrix # RANDOM 2-2
        - Numan, Gary - Music for chameleons, 1982; SR-24585; Numan, Gary (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24586. 2 copies.
        - Numan, Gary - Music for chameleons, 1982; SR-24586; Numan, Gary (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24585. 2 copies.
        - Numan, Gary - Dark light (the live EP), 1995; SR-24587; Numan, Gary (Box 375)
          Catalog # NUM 28; A-side Matrix # NUM-28-A1
        - Numan, Gary - Cars, 1987; SR-24588; Numan, Gary (Box 375)
        - Nunn, Bobby - She's just a groupie, 1982; SR-24589; Nunn, Bobby (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24590. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # PR-105; A-side Matrix # PR 105-A-66651-D-15B S13
        - Nunn, Bobby - She's just a groupie, 1982; SR-24590; Nunn, Bobby (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24589. 2 copies.Promo
        - Nunn, Bobby - She's just a groupie, 1982; SR-24591; Nunn, Bobby (Box 375)
          Catalog # 4502MG; A-side Matrix # 4502MG 66651-D-15B S13
        - Nunn, Bobby - Sexy sassy | Candy man, 1983; SR-24592; Nunn, Bobby; Mary Jane Girls (Box 375)
          Catalog # PR-115; A-side Matrix # PR-115-A-66769-D-15B
        - Nuri - Let's vote, 1980; SR-24593; Nuri (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24594. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TPR 1002; A-side Matrix # TPR-1002-A
          Tryon Park Records
        - Nuri - Let's vote, 1980; SR-24594; Nuri (Box 375)
          In same jacket as # SR-24593. 2 copies.
        - Nuri - Let's vote, 1980; SR-24595; Nuri (Box 376)
        - Nutta Butta - Freak out (remix), 1998; SR-24596; Nutta Butta; Riley, Teddy; B.B.O. (Box 376)
          Catalog # INT8P-6404; A-side Matrix # INT8P-6404-A
        - Nush - Nush, 1992; SR-24597; Nush (Box 376)
          Catalog # XTR 2T; A-side Matrix # XTR 2T-A1
          X:treme Records
        - Nutz - You gotta play this, 1990; SR-24598; Nutz (Box 376)
          No record company on the label or discogs
          Catalog # YGPT-1; A-side Matrix # YGPT-1-A
        - Nuwerk City Players - The feeling, 1996; SR-24599; Nuwerk City Players (Box 376)
          Catalog # CR-393; A-side Matrix # CR-393-A
        - Nuwerk City Players - Just can't forget, 1997; SR-24600; Nuwerk City Players (Box 376)
          Catalog # CR-409; A-side Matrix # CR-409-A
        - Nuyorican Soul - Nuyorican Soul (disc one), 1997; SR-24601; Nuyorican Soul; India; Ayers, Roy; Benson, George; Brown, Jocelyn; Levine, Mark (Box 376)
          In same jacket as # SR-24602. Double album.
          Catalog # 534 451.1; A-side Matrix # DFI 97 1 534460 1 AI
          Talkin' Loud
        - Nuyorican Soul - Nuyorican Soul (disc two), 1997; SR-24602; Nuyorican Soul; India; Ayers, Roy; Benson, George; Brown, Jocelyn; Levine, Mark (Box 376)
          In same jacket as # SR-24601. Double album.
          Catalog # 534 451.1; A-side Matrix # DFI 97 1 534461 1 AI
        - NV - Let me do you, 1984; SR-24603; NV (Box 376)
          Catalog # 0-20199; A-side Matrix # 0 20199A SH1 B-19145-SH1 6382
          Sire
        - N.W.A. - Panic zone, 1987; SR-24604; N.W.A. (Box 376)
          In same jacket as # SR-24605. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MRC-1034; A-side Matrix # L11 115-MRC-1034 L-28502
          Ruthless Records
        - N.W.A. - Panic zone, 1987; SR-24605; N.W.A. (Box 376)
          In same jacket as # SR-24604. 2 copies.
        - N.W.A. - Express yourself, 1989; SR-24606; N.W.A. (Box 376)
          Unsure the location of the label - Discogs is saying its from UK, but it may be the US
          Catalog # 12 BRX 144; A-side Matrix # 12 BRX 144 A1
        - N.W.A. And The Posse - N.W.A. and the Posse, 1987; SR-24607; N.W.A. And The Posse (Box 376)
          Catalog # MRC-LP 1057; A-side Matrix # MRC 1057-1
          Macola Record Co.
        - N.W.A. - Greatest hits (disc one), 1996; SR-24608; N.W.A. (Box 376)
          In same jacket as # SR-24609. Double album.
          Catalog # P1 50561; A-side Matrix # S-33538 RE1 P1-50561-A-RE1
          Priority Records
        - N.W.A. - Greatest hits (disc two), 1996; SR-24609; N.W.A. (Box 376)
          In same jacket as # SR-24608. Double album.
          Catalog # P1 50561; A-side Matrix # P1-50561-C-RE1 S-33540-RE1
        - N.W.A. - Straight outta Compton, 1988; SR-24610; N.W.A. (Box 376)
          Catalog # SL-57102; A-side Matrix # SL-1-57102-Z4
        - N.W.A. - Efil4zaggin, 1991; SR-24611; N.W.A. (Box 376)
          Catalog # SL 57126; A-side Matrix # SL-A-57126-21
        - N.W.A. - Chin check, 2000; SR-24612; N.W.A. (Box 376)
          Catalog # SPRO 81317; A-side Matrix # 81317-10-A 5-43350
        - N.W.A. - Greatest hits, 1996; SR-24613; N.W.A. (Box 376)
          In same jacket as # SR-24614. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # SPRO 30080; A-side Matrix # 81317-10-A 5-43350
        - N.W.A. - Greatest hits, 1996; SR-24614; N.W.A. (Box 376)
          In same jacket as # SR-24613. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # SPRO 30080; A-side Matrix # SPRO-30080-A S-33693
        - N.W.A. - Chin check, 2000; SR-24615; N.W.A. (Box 376)
        - N.W.A. - Straight outta Compton - 10th anniversary tribute, 1998; SR-24616; N.W.A.; Sikk The Shocker (Box 376)
          In same jacket as # SR-24617. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # SPRO 81104; A-side Matrix # SPRO-81104-A S-39201-RE-1
        - N.W.A. - Straight outta Compton - 10th anniversary tribute, 1998; SR-24617; N.W.A.; Sikk The Shocker (Box 376)
          In same jacket as # SR-24616. 2 copies.Promo
        - N.W.A. - Express yourself, 1989; SR-24618; N.W.A. (Box 376)
          Catalog # PVL-1-07271; A-side Matrix # VL-1-07271-Z1 B-35372 25054
        - N.W.A. - Gangsta gangsta, 1988; SR-24619; N.W.A. (Box 376)
          Catalog # VL-57105; A-side Matrix # VL-STREET-57105-Z1
        - Ny'a - I don't want you, 1994; SR-24620; Ny'a (Box 376)
          Catalog # E3T4B233; A-side Matrix # E-3-T-4-B-233-A
          Nap Records
          Jersey City, New Jersey
        - NYCC - I'll keep my light in my window, 1978; SR-24621; NYCC; New York Community Choir (Box 376)
          Catalog # JD-11372; A-side Matrix # PD-11372A-15
        - Nyhtjar - All in fun, 1983; SR-24622; Nyhtjar (Box 376)
          Catalog # PT-102; A-side Matrix # PT-102-A
          Partytime Records
        - Nytro - Nytro express, 1979; SR-24623; Nytro (Box 376)
          Catalog # WHID 8782; A-side Matrix # WHID-8782-WCA-8542-S-M1 24148
          Whitfield Records
        - Nasa - Shah Shah, 1990; SR-30831; Nasa (Box 376)
          Catalog # 0-21434; A-side Matrix # 0 21434 A SR1
        - New Deal - Receiver, 2001; SR-30832; New Deal (Box 376)
          Catalog # JDAB-42899; A-side Matrix # JDAB-42899-A
          Jive Electro
        - Nero, Peter - This is Peter Nero (disc one), 1972; SR-30953; Nero, Peter (Box 147)
          Catalog # VPS-6049; A-side Matrix # APRS-6935-2S
        - Nero, Peter - This is Peter Nero (disc two), 1972; SR-30954; Nero, Peter (Box 147)
          Catalog # VPS-6049; A-side Matrix # APRS-6937-2S
        - Numan, Gary - Warriors, 1983; SR-30955; Numan, Gary (Box 147)
          Catalog # BEG 95T; A-side Matrix # BEG 95T A-2U-1-2-X1
          London, England